Were you sleeping?
寝てた?
Yeah.
うん
Why are you sleeping?
なんで寝てるの?
What is that?
何だその?
I wonder what you're doing.
何してるのかなと
I want to sleep with you too.
俺も一緒に寝たい
I found it interesting.
僕は面白かったで
Don't sleep yet.
寝ないでよ、まだ
Will you do it again?
またするの?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Will you do it again?
またするの?
Because it hasn't been done yet.
だってまだ全然してないじゃん
Not enough?
足んない?
Well, you don't have a big enough penis, do you?
まあ、ちんちん足んないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Is it enough?
足りた?
Yeah.
うん
My pillow has stopped.
枕止まれてきた
What?
え、何?
what?
何?
Why weren't you sleeping like that?
なんでそんな寝てたんじゃないの?
picture?
え?
Weren't you asleep?
寝てたんじゃないの?
I can't let you sleep.
寝かせてくんないじゃん
Look here.
こっち見て
I think I'm going to sleep.
寝そうじゃん
Yeah.
うん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Down there?
あんな下のに?
Does it still feel good?
まだ気持ちいいの?
Down there?
あんな下のに?
Yeah.
うん
That far down?
あんないっぱい下のに?
It feels so good.
すっごい気持ちいい
Can I take it out?
出 していい?
I'll put it out.
出すよ